DENIS YURKOV

UNITY DEVELOPER

linkedin.com/in/denisyurkov in

dzianisyurkou@gmail.com

denisyurkov.github.io



+48 517 149 671



PROFILE

Games are magic, it's a completely different form of art. That's why I chose to make games because it's real magic. What inspires me the most is the team spirit that comes with game development. I have been developing games for more than 2 years. And after a while I can say for sure that I chose the right

EXPERIENCES

Robot Gentleman

Unity Developer (Intern) Jul 2022 - Sep 2022 · 3 mos

 Developing climate and environment themed project led by Robot Gentleman

Self-employed

Unity Developer Jan 2021 - Dec 2021 · 1 yr

• I went through a full cycle of creating a game in a

- Developed several games myself and in a team.
- Programming the game logic, core mechanics, and led
- Working with a game designer, graphics and other programmers.

Rock Game

Unity Developer (Intern) Jul 2021 - Oct 2021 · 4 mos

- Developing Hyper Casual Games
- Optimizing games for mobile devices
- Creating prototypes and game core mechanics

EDUCATION

Collegium Da Vinci (Poznań, Poland)

2020 - Present | Engineer of game and interactive media design

SKILLS

- Unity
- C#
- Git
- OOP Principles
- Design Patterns
- SOLID
- Zenject

LANGUAGES

Polsih C1

B2 English

Belarusian **Native**

Russian Native

AGREEMENT

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).